[
{
    "question": "Man: Can I have one coffee and two teas, please?<br>Waitress: I'm sorry. The coffee machine's just being fixed.<br>What does the waitress mean?",
    "options": ["A. I can make coffee, but not tea.", "B. I can't make coffee at the moment.", "C. I can only make a drink from the machine."],
    "answer": "B. I can't make coffee at the moment."
},
{
    "question": "Woman: I'm cold, Jim. Have you got a sweater?<br>Man: Yes, but it's not very clean, I'm afraid.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. Can you lend me a sweater?", "B. Do you still have my sweater?", "C. Why aren't you wearing a sweater?"],
    "answer": "A. Can you lend me a sweater?"
},
{
    "question": "Woman: I've got a terrible headache!<br>Man: Why don't you lie down for a while?<br>What does the man mean?",
    "options": ["A. He is criticising the woman.", "B. He is giving the woman some advice.", "C. He is asking the woman for information."],
    "answer": "B. He is giving the woman some advice."
},
{
    "question": "Male shop assistant: Have you seen the new Sales Manager?<br>Female shop assistant: Yes, what's she like?<br>What does the female shop assistant mean?",
    "options": ["A. What does she look like?", "B. What do you like about her?", "C. What can you tell me about her?"],
    "answer": "A. What does she look like?"
},
{
    "question": "Man: It's a nice day for a drive in the countryside.<br>Woman: Yes, but I'm a bit busy this afternoon.<br>The man.....",
    "options": ["A. Suggesting a trip to the countryside.", "B. Agreeing to drive the woman to the countryside.", "C. Finding out about the weather in the countryside."],
    "answer": "A. Suggesting a trip to the countryside."
},
{
    "question": "Man: Can you start work immediately?<br>Woman: No, but I can begin in two weeks.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. She doesn't want the job.", "B. She can't start working now.", "C. She didn't work for two weeks."],
    "answer": "B. She can't start working now."
},
{
    "question": "Man: I'm not going to bother washing the car. It's going to rain later.<br>Woman: Yes, I heard that on the news this morning.<br>What does the man mean?",
    "options": ["A. He won't wash his car.", "B. His car isn't very dirty.", "C. He doesn't like the rain."],
    "answer": "A. He won't wash his car."
},
{
    "question": "Woman: I'm sorry. I forgot to wash the dishes this morning.<br>Man: It's okay. I did them when I got home.<br>What does the man mean?",
    "options": ["A. He can't do the dishes later.", "B. He wants the woman to wash the dishes.", "C. The woman doesn't need to wash the dishes."],
    "answer": "C. The woman doesn't need to wash the dishes."
},
{
    "question": "Man: This vacation has been wonderful.<br>Woman: Can we come back next year?<br>Man: If you'd like to, sure.<br>What does the man mean by his SECOND comment?",
    "options": ["A. We can return to this place.", "B. I'm not sure if we can come back.", "C. You like this place more than I do."],
    "answer": "A. We can return to this place."
},
{
    "question": "Man: Do you know where the class is meeting for dinner?<br>Woman: At Thai Lotus Restaurant, right next to the main school building.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. The restaurant is close to school.", "B. People will have dinner on the beach.", "C. The class will meet at the main building."],
    "answer": "A. The restaurant is close to school."
},
{
    "question": "Man: I made some soup. Would you like some?<br>Woman: No thanks. I don't feel like eating at the moment.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. She isn't very hungry.", "B. She isn't enjoying the soup.", "C. She doesn't have time to eat."],
    "answer": "A. She isn't very hungry."
},
{
    "question": "Teacher: Don't forget your bag!<br>Student: Oh, that bag isn't mine.<br>What does the teacher mean?",
    "options": ["A. You don't usually forget to take your bag.", "B. Try to remember to take your bag next time.", "C. Remember to take your bag when you leave."],
    "answer": "C. Remember to take your bag when you leave."
},
{
    "question": "Man: I really need to take my computer to the shop. It's broken again.<br>Woman: Do you want to use mine?<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. The man needs to call the computer repair store.", "B. The man can use the woman's computer.", "C. The man should buy a new computer."],
    "answer": "B. The man can use the woman's computer."
},
{
    "question": "Student: Bye then sir!<br>Teacher: Bye Sam - and do make an effort to come to class on time tomorrow!<br>Student: I'll try, sir!<br>What does the teacher mean?",
    "options": ["A. You were late for the class today.", "B. You don't try hard enough in class.", "C. You must find out the time of the class tomorrow."],
    "answer": "A. You were late for the class today."
},
{
    "question": "Man: Do you work on Mondays?<br>Woman: No, I only work on weekends.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. She is finished with her work.", "B. She works every day of the week.", "C. She works on Saturday and Sunday."],
    "answer": "C. She works on Saturday and Sunday."
},
{
    "question": "Man: What time do you finish work today?<br>Woman: I work from 10 a.m. to 2 p.m.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. She works until 2 p.m.", "B. She begins work at 2 p.m.", "C. She finishes work at 10 a.m."],
    "answer": "A. She works until 2 p.m."
},
{
    "question": "Man: Excuse me. Can you pass me the dictionary?<br>Woman: Sure. No problem. Here you are.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. I don't have it.", "B. I am looking for it.", "C. I can give it to you."],
    "answer": "C. I can give it to you."
},
{
    "question": "Man: When I was growing up, my cousin's family would always come over to our place for the holidays.<br>Woman: I wish I could say the same! Mine lived so far away.<br>Man: Yes, we were pretty fortunate.<br>What does the woman mean?",
    "options": ["A. She often likes to talk about family holidays.", "B. She rarely got to see her cousins on holidays.", "C. She usually traveled long distances for holidays."],
    "answer": "B. She rarely got to see her cousins on holidays."
}

]